leva Baranauskaite

Tel: 07397803602

E-mail: <u>ieva.b.1987@gmail.com</u>
GitHub: https://github.com/1Eva1987

LinkedIn https://linkedin.com/in/ieva-baranauskaite-096773252

12 Highcliff Gardens, Scunthorpe, DN158JJ

PERSONAL SUMMARY

As a highly motivated and adaptable team player, I am searching for a Junior Developer role that would allow me to further develop as an IT professional and grow within a challenging environment. I am a fast learner and work well under pressure combined with strong organizational and detail-oriented skills, I am confident that I can contribute to any web development team. I am thrilled to have the opportunity to showcase my work and share my passion with you through my portfolio. It is my hope that my projects and experiences will convey my enthusiasm for coding and the value I can bring to any team or project.

WEB TECHNOLOGY AND SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SKILLS:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, React, Node js.

KEY COMPETENCIES AND SKILLS

- Excellent customer service skills honed through several customer-facing roles.
- Strong organizational and time management skills.
- Ability to learn fast, especially when acquiring new technical skills.
- Able to work well under pressure, meeting tight deadlines in busy environments.
- Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal, in Lithuanian, English, and intermediate Russian.
- Good numerical and analytical skills, with experience using modern computerized equipment.
- Languages: Lithuanian native, English fluent, Russian intermediate.

EDUCATION AND IT TRAININGS

- Trilogy's Skills Bootcamp in Front-End Development- edX Certificate of Completion 2023
- MRU University of Law, Vilnius, Lithuania 2005 2010

CAREER HISTORY

Care Assistant Sycamore Lodge nursing and residential care home - Scunthorpe, UK February 2017 - September 2022

Sales Assistant, Manager KAUPTE clothing store, Lithuania, Panevezys June 2014 – November 2016

- Ensured cashiers followed accounting policies, safety procedures, and customer service standards.
- Ensured customer transactions were processed promptly and accurately.
- Evaluated performance of cashiers and provided feedback.
- Performed bank deposits and withdrawals according to established policies.

• Generated cash-related documents and account reports.

Manager MIRAGE and CLEOPATRA nightclubs, Lithuania, Vilnius October 2009 – March 2012

- Met visitors and organized staff work.
- Hired and trained qualified employees.
- Oversaw the process of ordering club supplies.
- Achieved quotas in sales and profit margins.

DRIVER LICENSE

B category license. Own transport